<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS Modernization Workshop with CoreStack on MP DevOps Series</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS Modernization Workshop with CoreStack on MP DevOps Series</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. AWS Account Setup</title>
      <link>/030_self_guided_setup/30_aws_setup_your_own.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_self_guided_setup/30_aws_setup_your_own.html</guid>
      <description>Setting up your AWS account  You are responsible for the cost of the AWS services used while running this workshop in your AWS account. We highly recommend you to go to the request AWS credit page so you can run this workshop without any charge to you.
  If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have an AWS account with Administrator access: create one now by clicking here
 Once you have an AWS account, ensure you are following the remaining workshop steps as an IAM user with administrator access to the AWS account: Create a new IAM user to use for the workshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. CoreStack Account Setup</title>
      <link>/040_corestack_setup/40_corestack_setup_onboarding.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/040_corestack_setup/40_corestack_setup_onboarding.html</guid>
      <description>CoreStack Account Setup (Onboarding) Please go to the CoreStack Dashboard. Login with the email and password you used to sign up! There should be a confirmation email sent with your login information. Your greeting page should look like this:  Click the GET STARTED button and choose AWS as the public cloud on the next page  Click the Assessment + Governance option, Linked Account option, AWS Standard option, and the AssumeRole authentication option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Onboarding an AWS account​</title>
      <link>/050_corestack_lab/50_onboard_aws_account.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/050_corestack_lab/50_onboard_aws_account.html</guid>
      <description>Onboarding an AWS account using CFN template for role creation ​  Please go to the CoreStack Dashboard. Login with the email and password you used to sign up! There should be a confirmation email sent with your login information. Your greeting page should look like this:  Click the GET STARTED button and choose AWS as the public cloud on the next page  Click the Assessment + Governance option, Linked Account option, AWS Standard option, and the AssumeRole authentication option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreword</title>
      <link>/010_introduction/10_foreword.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/010_introduction/10_foreword.html</guid>
      <description>How did we get here? The cloud lies at the heart of any enterprise digital transformation initiative, but there are numerous challenges with cloud adoption:
 Unabated &amp;amp; Wasted Cloud Costs
Security &amp;amp; Compliance Issues
Cloud Operational Complexities
 With 92% of enterprises operating from a multi-cloud strategy, with an average of 2.6 public clouds, today’s organization often find themselves overshooting cloud budgets, accidentally exposing data or services and not continuously optimizing cloud workloads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. CoreStack Sign Up</title>
      <link>/030_self_guided_setup/31_corestack_mp_trial.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_self_guided_setup/31_corestack_mp_trial.html</guid>
      <description>Signing up for CoreStack via AWS Marketplace  Visit CoreStack in AWS Marketplace You&amp;rsquo;ll land here  Click the Try for free button on the top right-hand corner. You may be prompted to sign in to the AWS account you just created, or the one you will be using for this workshop:  Click the 14 Day Free Trial option and your page should look like this:  Click the Create contract button in the purchase box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. CoreStack Templates</title>
      <link>/050_corestack_lab/35_create_apply_templates.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/050_corestack_lab/35_create_apply_templates.html</guid>
      <description>Create and apply templates CoreStack™ also provides the option for users to upload their own templates and use them to execute against their service accounts. Follow the steps given below: Use the ‘+’ button next to the ‘Search’ bar at top right.
Template create window will have 3 sections as follows: Properties, Content and Metadata.
Lists all template executions of the current tenant. A sample screenshot is shown below. The tabs at the top right represents the archive status of jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Infra as code – use cases</title>
      <link>/050_corestack_lab/50_infra_as_code.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/050_corestack_lab/50_infra_as_code.html</guid>
      <description>Infra as code – use cases Provisioning of VM using CFN / Terraform CFN Template Source
Provisioning a DB using CFN / Terraform CFN Template Source
Provisioning a Container using CFN / Terraform CFN Template Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. AWS Credit Request</title>
      <link>/030_self_guided_setup/32_request_credit.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_self_guided_setup/32_request_credit.html</guid>
      <description>To help you cover the AWS service costs incurred by doing this tutorial, AWS Credits are available courtesy of AWS Marketplace. Submit the form and you will receive a confirmation email with an AWS Credit Code. Credits are available while supplies last.  Request AWS Credits         AWS Marketplace is a digital software catalog that makes it easy to find, try, buy, deploy, and manage software that works with AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Problem to Solve</title>
      <link>/010_introduction/12_problem_to_solve.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/010_introduction/12_problem_to_solve.html</guid>
      <description>Business Problem to Solve  79% of surveyed organizations indicate that managing cloud spend is a challenge and that 30% of spend is wasted. 80% of organizations overshoot their cloud IaaS budgets, 50% accidentally expose data or services, and 47% do not continuously optimize cloud workloads (source: Gartner). 81% of organizations indicate cloud security is a primary challenge, with 95% of issues stemming from misconfigurations (source: Gartner), and 75% from inefficient cloud operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Validation of the Infra provisioned against AWS Well Architected Framework</title>
      <link>/050_corestack_lab/54_well-architected_validation.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/050_corestack_lab/54_well-architected_validation.html</guid>
      <description>Validation of the Infra provisioned against AWS Well Architected Framework Execute some policies to validate certain AWS Well Architected Framework Controls in the resources provisioned
 CoreStack has support for a growing list of Industry specific Regulatory Compliance standard and Industry benchmark standards necessary for modern corporations in various sectors. CoreStack is committed in bringing industry leading technology in cloud governance with the ease of use unrivaled in today’s complicated tech landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is CoreStack</title>
      <link>/010_introduction/14_partner.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/010_introduction/14_partner.html</guid>
      <description>What is CoreStack? CoreStack empowers enterprises to unleash the power of cloud on their terms by helping them rapidly achieve continuous and autonomous cloud governance at scale. CoreStack enables enterprises to realize:​</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Post-Onboarding</title>
      <link>/040_corestack_setup/42_post_onboarding.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/040_corestack_setup/42_post_onboarding.html</guid>
      <description>Post-Onboarding Once you have completed adding your cloud accounts into CoreStack, you can see them listed as part of the Account Summary Dashboard.
From the Account Governance Dashboard, select the cloud account you want to review, and click on “View Settings”. Click on the Assessment Validation tab on the left-hand side. You&amp;rsquo;ll see this:
Click the RE-VALIDATE button to re-assess the infrastructure in your account. Feel free to play around and check out the other 4 pillars and see what permissions are allowed for which resources in your account!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. Execute templates/scripts that will remediate the violation </title>
      <link>/050_corestack_lab/55_remediate_violation.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/050_corestack_lab/55_remediate_violation.html</guid>
      <description>Execute templates/scripts that will remediate the violation Script is a single or multiple file that contains a sequence of commands a program that are used for automation. CoreStack™ supports commonly used automation tools such as Chef, Ansible, Puppet and Shell (Bash and PowerShell).
CoreStack™ provides a wide range of pre-defined scripts which can help in realizing multiple use cases. These are pre-loaded for all subscriptions and are FREE to be executed on-demand or scheduled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conclusion</title>
      <link>/050_corestack_lab/56_conclusion.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/050_corestack_lab/56_conclusion.html</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip;.Beginning of September for *Auto-remediation*</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well Architected Framework: Continuous Governance</title>
      <link>/010_introduction/18_waf.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/010_introduction/18_waf.html</guid>
      <description> Well Architected Framework: Continuous Governance  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Next Steps</title>
      <link>/010_introduction/16_workshop_next_step.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/010_introduction/16_workshop_next_step.html</guid>
      <description>Workshop Prerequisites There are a few prerequisite tasks you must perform before getting started on this workshop. These are:​
 Access to an AWS account with proper permissions​ Sign-up for a CoreStack trial account​ Access to GitHub and writes to run a CFT or Terraform Template​  In the next section, you will be instructed on how to configure all the prerequisite tasks stated above.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
