<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Event Engine</title>
    <link>/ee/010_introduction.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Event Engine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/ee/010_introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Foreword</title>
      <link>/ee/010_introduction/10_foreword.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ee/010_introduction/10_foreword.html</guid>
      <description>How did we get here? The cloud lies at the heart of any enterprise digital transformation initiative, but there are numerous challenges with cloud adoption:​
 Unabated &amp;amp; Wasted Cloud Costs​ Security &amp;amp; Compliance Issues​ Cloud Operational Complexities​  With 92% of enterprises operating from a multi-cloud strategy, with an average of 2.6 public clouds, today’s organization often find themselves overshooting cloud budgets, accidentally exposing data or services and not continuously optimizing cloud workloads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Problem to Solve</title>
      <link>/ee/010_introduction/12_problem_to_solve.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ee/010_introduction/12_problem_to_solve.html</guid>
      <description>Business Problem to Solve  79% of surveyed organizations indicate that managing cloud spend is a challenge and that 30% of spend is wasted. ​ 80% of organizations overshoot their cloud IaaS budgets, 50% accidentally expose data or services, and 47% do not continuously optimize cloud workloads (source: Gartner).​ 81% of organizations indicate cloud security is a primary challenge, with 95% of issues stemming from misconfigurations (source: Gartner), and 75% from inefficient cloud operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is CoreStack</title>
      <link>/ee/010_introduction/14_partner.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ee/010_introduction/14_partner.html</guid>
      <description>What is CoreStack? CoreStack empowers enterprises to unleash the power of cloud on their terms by helping them rapidly achieve continuous and autonomous cloud governance at scale. CoreStack enables enterprises to realize:​</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Next Steps</title>
      <link>/ee/010_introduction/16_workshop_next_step.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ee/010_introduction/16_workshop_next_step.html</guid>
      <description> Workshop Prerequisites There are a few prerequisite tasks you must perform before getting started on this workshop. These are:​
 Access to an AWS account with proper permissions​ Sign-up for a CoreStack trial account​ Access to GitHub and writes to run a CFT or Terraform Template​  In the next section, you will be instructed on how to configure all the prerequisite tasks stated above.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
