<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Self Guided Setup on MP DevOps Series</title>
    <link>/030_self_guided_setup.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self Guided Setup on MP DevOps Series</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/030_self_guided_setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. AWS Account Setup</title>
      <link>/030_self_guided_setup/30_aws_setup_your_own.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_self_guided_setup/30_aws_setup_your_own.html</guid>
      <description>Setting up your AWS account  You are responsible for the cost of the AWS services used while running this workshop in your AWS account. We highly recommend you to go to the request AWS credit page so you can run this workshop without any charge to you.
  If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have an AWS account with Administrator access: create one now by clicking here
 Once you have an AWS account, ensure you are following the remaining workshop steps as an IAM user with administrator access to the AWS account: Create a new IAM user to use for the workshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. CoreStack Sign Up</title>
      <link>/030_self_guided_setup/31_corestack_mp_trial.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_self_guided_setup/31_corestack_mp_trial.html</guid>
      <description>Signing up for CoreStack via AWS Marketplace  Visit CoreStack in AWS Marketplace You&amp;rsquo;ll land here  Click the Try for free button on the top right-hand corner. You may be prompted to sign in to the AWS account you just created, or the one you will be using for this workshop:  Click the 14 Day Free Trial option and your page should look like this:  Click the Create contract button in the purchase box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. AWS Credit Request</title>
      <link>/030_self_guided_setup/32_request_credit.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/030_self_guided_setup/32_request_credit.html</guid>
      <description>To help you cover the AWS service costs incurred by doing this tutorial, AWS Credits are available courtesy of AWS Marketplace. Submit the form and you will receive a confirmation email with an AWS Credit Code. Credits are available while supplies last.  Request AWS Credits         AWS Marketplace is a digital software catalog that makes it easy to find, try, buy, deploy, and manage software that works with AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
